Contact

me@anthonywd.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ anthonyaguayo (LinkedIn) www.anthonywd.com (Personal)

Top Skills

CSS

HTML5

jQuery

Languages

English

Honors-Awards

Moboom's 2014 Developer Day Winner

Moboom's 2014 Highest Selling Template

Anthony Aguayo

Detail-oriented Multimedia Designer Based in Northern California Sacramento

Summary

Eight years of Multimedia experience all over Northern California. Graphic Design and or Front End Developed for The Sacramento Kings, The Sacramento D.A. Office and more! Working experience both in an agency on a team overseeing 400+ clients, and in-house as the lead guy. I'm detail-oriented with front end development and out of the box with my graphic design!

Experience

Humidi.co
Graphic Designer & Web Developer
February 2020 - Present (8 months)
Sacramento, California, United States

Current full-time solo in house Graphic Designer & Web Developer. Graphic Design print and digital projects I've worked on so far include Brochures / Catalogs, Pricing Lists & Order Forms, Fliers, Stickers, Business Cards, Logos, Product Mockups, Custom Product Packaging (both in-house and design agency), Product Photo Editing, Social Media Posts & Advertisements, and more each day! In addition as the Web Designer / Developer I write HTML, CSS & Bootstrap to build web pages and maintain the current Wordpress & Woo-commerce (e-commerce) built website. I also Install / Update all plugins, backup the website database, and create bi-monthly reports for management. Since starting through hard work we've integrated Seller Zen, Quick Books Online, My Works, SOS Inventory, Shipstation and Hubspot to all work harmoniously and assist staff by making work easier for them. Additional work experience and responsibilities include Product Photography, Video Editing, Project Management and fun fact on one project Hand Modeling Iol! Some of the programs and tools I use each week include Adobe (Photoshop, Illustrator, In Design, XD, Dreamweaver, After Effects, Premier, Audition), Canon (EOS Rebel T7i, EF50mm f/1.8 STM Lens, EF-S18-55mm f/4-5.6 IS STM Lens, Canon Pixma ip8720 printer) and Lomia Studio Lighting Kit.

Shield N Seal

Graphic Designer & Web Developer February 2020 - Present (8 months)

Sacramento, California, United States

Current full-time solo in house Graphic Designer & Web Developer. Graphic Design print and digital projects I've worked on so far include Brochures / Catalogs, Pricing Lists & Order Forms, Fliers, Stickers, Business Cards, Logos, Product Mockups, Custom Product Packaging (both in-house and design agency), Product Photo Editing, Social Media Posts & Advertisements, and more each day! In addition as the Web Designer / Developer I write HTML, CSS & Bootstrap to build web pages and maintain the current Wordpress & Woo-commerce (e-commerce) built website. I also Install / Update all plugins. backup the website database, and create bi-monthly reports for management. Since starting through hard work we've integrated Seller Zen, Quick Books Online, My Works, SOS Inventory, Shipstation and Hubspot to all work harmoniously and assist staff by making work easier for them. Additional work experience and responsibilities include Product Photography, Video Editing, Project Management and fun fact on one project Hand Modeling Iol! Some of the programs and tools I use each week include Adobe (Photoshop, Illustrator, In Design, XD, Dreamweaver, After Effects, Premier, Audition), Canon (EOS Rebel T7i, EF50mm f/1.8 STM Lens, EF-S18-55mm f/4-5.6 IS STM Lens, Canon Pixma ip8720 printer) and Lomia Studio Lighting Kit.

AnthonyWD Multimedia Designer March 2012 - Present (8 years 7 months) Sacramento, California Area

https://www.anthonywd.com/ Graphic Design (Print, Digital, Apparel)

Front End Development (HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Foundation, Wordpress)
Multimedia Design (Audio & Video Editing, Photography, Motion Graphics)
UI/UX (QA testing, A/B Testing, User-flows, Wireframes, Mock-ups)

4Parts Design
Graphic & Web Designer
March 2018 - September 2018 (7 months)
Sausalito, California

During my time with 4parts Design I assisted in Graphic Design, product photography and lead all of the Web Development projects. Utilizing my Graphic Design experience I designed wine labels, wine corks, packaging design, wine tasting note cards, event flyers, stickers, posters, icons, logos, business cards, letterheads, infographics, banner ads, company

branded merchandise and more. As the lead website developer at 4parts I developed wireframes, mockups, user flows, email newsletters, Shopify sites, Squarespace sites, integrated third party plugins and built custom responsive websites on the Wordpress platform utilizing HTML & CSS with the occasional Bootstrap framework. In addition to my Graphic and Web Design work I also helped to record / edit media (video / audio), take product / lifestyle photography, and help in animation creation.

AVB Marketing
Digital & Web Designer
February 2017 - March 2018 (1 year 2 months)
Sacramento, California

As a Digital / Web Designer for AVB Marketing I designed digital advertisements (Wireframes, Banners, Google HTML5 Ads, and Facebook Ads) for over 400+ family owned businesses in the appliance, electronics and furniture industry. We designed advertisements for our clients promoting various holidays, sales, and manufacturer brands (Maytag, Whirlpool, GE, KitchenAid, Samsung, LG, Sony, Serta and various others). In addition to my design experience management put me in charge of creating a framework (HTML, CSS, Media Queries, Flexbox, and B.E.M. naming convention) for their team of 14 designers, and to assist the designers in cutting down their production time from eight hours to four. I was tasked with creating various website landing page templates, quality checking all the designers' code, and training the designers through documentation and video tutorials. The code I produced assisted the AVB Marketing design team in producing over 400+ websites in under six months, transitioning some of their clients from table based fixed layouts to fully responsive static layouts, but during my time with AVB Marketing I personally built over 180+ websites.

Moboom Junior Client Engineer August 2013 - July 2016 (3 years) San Francisco Bay Area

Initially I started out as a Technology Evangelist for Moboom, where my role was to learn their platform and teach it to the public online and at shows. Mobooms platform allows for visitors to build a website with no coding experience necessary; I.E. SquareSpace, Wix or Weebly, through the use of pre built templates which I was also tasked with creating. After learning the Moboom platform I took part in their annual Moboom Developers Day 2013; I won gained full-time position and new job role Junior Client Engineer.

While a Jr. Client Engineer I took my experience with what customers were asking for through A/B Testing and built new templates. Helped the back end development team Q/A test for bugs and even aided in tech support to the public through chat, webinars, and forum assistance. In total I helped to design over 200 responsive templates; one for the National Australian Bank, over three individual products.

T.I.M. (Adult Media)
Graphic Designer & Jr Front End Developer
November 2012 - August 2013 (10 months)
San Francisco Bay Area

Graphic Design work entailed designing semi monthly DVD product packaging and disc art; for three adult media producers, along with accompanying social media advertisement banners and print work. The print work included posters, apparel, magazines stickers and more! In addition to my Graphic Design role I was the Jr. Front End Developer building new product pages; with HTML 5 and CSS 3, coding the monthly newsletter and I helped to produce the semi monthly eBooks.

Infusion Lounge
Junior Developer
March 2012 - October 2012 (8 months)
San Francisco Bay Area

While I was the Junior Developer for Infusion Lounge; the night club & hotel, I had my hand on a wide variety of projects. Graphic Design work included business cards, letterheads, night club flyers, hotel room keys, gift cards, drink coasters, social media graphics, apparel design, UX / UI web landing page mockups and even conceptualizing a RedBull Flug Tag entry participant. On the development side I helped to maintain their Wordpress; with Woocommerce integration for eCommerce, website by adding / editing products and creating any new pages needed.

Sacramento Kings
Apparel Designer
October 2010 - December 2010 (3 months)
Sacramento, California Area

The Sacramento Kings were hosting two separate competitions; one in October & one in December, for local artist to create limited edition apparel for the Sacramento Kings. The limited edition apparel was sold under the title Artist's Collection. In total I sold three shirts and was featured in two half time

shows promoting my apparel. One of the shirts based on N.B.A. player Tyreke Evans was purchased separately to be sold online and in the team store for the next three full N.B.A. Seasons!

See the winning apparel on my online portfolio located at anthonywd.com/ portfolio

Education

The Art Institute of California-Sacramento
Bachelor of Applied Science (BASc), Web Design an Interactive
Media · (2008 - 2012)

Art Institute of Houston
Associates Degree, Graphic Design · (2005 - 2007)